Have an important question for you why are you pursuing the PMP.
Why do you want to be a PMP.
What's it going to bring to you is that an ambition.
It's going to make you a better project manager sort of financial reward.
So why are you doing the PMP.
Well we're talking about benefits in this section.
So what benefits will the PMP bring to you and to your organization and your customers.
So what want you to make a connection here between the PMP it's a test it's a very tough challenging
test.
It's a lots of terms to know a lot of information to know.
But how is that going to make you a better person not just a project manager but a better person.
I think it gives you confidence in your life that you've overcome a challenge in that.
That's great.
It's a realization of ambition.
It is the ability for others to put trust and confidence in you because obviously you've done the work.
You have experience and you have insight into the generally accepted practices of project management.
So those are all benefits.
But what other benefits might you have somebody that takes some time and think about that like how is
this really benefiting me as an individual.
You know for me it's opened up a lot of doors and created opportunity but it also helped me become a
better project manager to think more about just getting from A to B but to think about getting from
A to B to C to D all the way to the end.
There's a lot more moving parts and components.
So over the years as a project manager you know we learn it's not always the shortest route.
Sometimes we have to accommodate stakeholders and accommodate politics and other factors that can really
seem to interrupt our project.
Well the truth is that's part of project management.
So I want you to think about the benefits as to what is this going to do in your career and in your
life.
All right.
You're doing great you're making great progress.
Keep it up.
I'll see you in the next lecture.